Guide to the American Dance Festival Photographic Materials Collection, circa 1930-2008
American Dance Festival Archives
- Company and Biographical, circa 1930-2008
  - Maharaj, Briju Maharaj and Company, undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Malale, Amiel, 1991, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Malashock, John, undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Manhattan Project, 1974, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Mantero, Vera, 1996, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Mantero, Vera, 1996, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Marcade, Caroline Marcade et Compagnie, circa 1983, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Marginalii, 1994, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Marin, Compagnie Maguy Marin, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Marin, Maguy, 1983, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheet) (Box 30)
  - Marin, Maguy, circa 1994, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Marshall, Barak, 1998-1999, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Marshall, Barak, ICCP, 1994, 1999, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Marshall, Jay, undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Marshall, Jay, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 30)
  - Marshall, Susan Marshall Company, 1995, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Martin, Erin, 1970, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Martin, John, 1964, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Martinez, Lydia, 1989, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Maslow, Sophie Maslow and Company, 1950, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Matteo, 1964, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Matteo, 1964-1965, (35 mm slides, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheet) (Box 30)
  - Matteo, undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Mattox, Matt, 1998, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Mattox, Matt, 1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets, 35 mm color negatives, 5 x 7 b&w negative) (Box 30)
  - McGriff, Haywood "Woody", undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - McIntyre, Dianne, 1993, (prints) (Box 12)
  - McIntyre, Dianne, 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - McKayle, Donald, 1963-1964, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - McKayle, Donald, 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - McKayle, Donald, 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - McKayle, Donald, 1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - McKayle, Donald, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - McKayle, Donald, Classes, 1986, 1992-1993, 2000, 2002, (prints) (Box 12)
  - McKayle, Donald, Classes, circa 1960-1969, (prints) (Box 12)
  - McKayle, Donald, Portraits, 2002, undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - McKayle, Donald, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 30)
  - McKayle, Donald McKayle and Company, 1963, (35 mm slides) (Box 30)
  - McKayle, Donald McKayle and Company, Arena, undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - McKayle, Donald McKayle and Company, Dances, undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - McKayle, Donald McKayle and Company, District Storyville, undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - McKayle, Donald McKayle and Company, Games, undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - McKayle, Donald McKayle and Company, Rainbow 'Round My Shoulder, undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - McLean, Gloria, undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Meehan, Nancy, 1973, 1976, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Meier, Jose, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Meissner, Ann, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 30)
  - Meissner, Anne, 1982, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Metropolitan Opera Ballet Ensemble, 1976, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Midgette, Carlton, 1998, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Mitchell, Arthur, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Mitha, Tehreema, 1990, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Monk, Meredith, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Monk, Meredith, 2001, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Monk, Meredith, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negatives, 5 x 7 b&w negatives) (Box 30)
  - Monk, Meredith/The House, 1969-1970, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Monk, Meredith/The House, 2001, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Mooney, Elina, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Moore, Carman, 1992, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Moore, Jack, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Morris, Mark, 1984, 1994, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Morris, Mark, 1984, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Morris, Mark, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Morris, Mark Morris Dance Group 2002, (35 mm color contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Morris, Mark Morris Dance Group, 1994, 1996, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Morris, Mark Morris Dance Group, 1996, (35 mm slide, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Morris, Mark Morris Dance Group, 2000, (35 mm slides, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Morris, Mark Morris Dance Group, 2000, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Morris, Mark Morris Dance Group, 2000, 2002, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Morris, Mark Morris Dance Group, circa 1994, (35 mm b&w copy slides) (Box 30)
  - Moulton, Charles Moulton Dance Company, circa 1982, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Muller, Jennifer Muller and the Works, circa 1982, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Multigravitational Experiment Group, circa 1974, 1977, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Musard, Yves, 1986, 1988, 1989, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Mussman, Marjorie, 1991, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Myers, Gerald E., 1994, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Myers, Martha, 1972, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 30)
  - Myers, Martha, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Myers, Martha, 1996-1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Myers, Martha, 1996-1998, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Myers, Martha, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Myers, Martha, Portraits and Other Professional Photos, 1988-2001, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Myers, Martha, Snapshots, 1994-1998, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Myers, Martha, Teaching, 1994-2001, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Nagrin, Daniel, 1959, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Nagrin, Daniel, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 30)
  - Nagrin, Daniel, The Workgroup, 1972, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Nagrin, Daniel, undated, (4 x 5 b&w negative) (Box 30)
  - Najan, Nala, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - National Company of Song and Dance of Mozambique, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Neville, Phoebe, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Newman, Gloria, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Next Ice Age, 1997, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Next Ice Age, 1998 (2 folders), (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Nicholas Brothers and Sisters, circa 1998, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Nicholas, Fayard, 1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Nicholas, Fayard, 1998, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Nicks, Walter, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Nicks, Walter Nicks Dance Theater, circa 1977, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Nielson, Doug, 1997, 2000, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Nielson, Doug, 1997, 2000, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Nikolais, Alwin, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Nikolais, Alwin Nikolais Dance Theater, undated, (35 mm slides) (Box 30)
  - Nikolais and Murray Louis Dance, 1994, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Nikolais and Murray Louis Dance, 1994, (8 x 10 b&w negative, 4 x 5 b&w negative) (Box 30)
  - Nikolais Dance Company, 1985, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Nikolais Dance Theater, Performance, 1984, 1985, (prints) (Box 13)
  - Nikolais Dance Theater, Publicity, 1976, 1980, undated, (prints) (Box 13)
  - North Carolina Dance Theatre, 1981, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - North Carolina Dance Theatre, circa 1981, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Nucleodanza, 1989, (8 x 10 b&w negative, 4 x 5 b&w negative) (Box 30)
  - Nucleodanza, A Certain Death, Like An Octopus, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Nucleodanza, Cadaver Equisto, The Other Mirror, 1989, 1992, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Nucleodanza, Company Members, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Nucleodanza, Fold Woman Along Dotted Lines, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Nucleodanza, La Espera, 4 Entres Tiempos, 1989, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Nucleodanza, Performance, Publicity, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Nucleodanza, Playing With Fire, Patagonia Song and Dance Team, 1989, 1992, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Nucleodanza, The Mourning Kiss, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Nucleodanza, The Stab, A Night with Gardel, 1989, 1992, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Nucleodanza, Tilt, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Nucleodanza, Two on the Cornice, 1995, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Nucleodanza, undated, (35 mm slide) (Box 30)
  - Nuevo Treato de la Danza, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Nugent, Jennifer, 2001, (prints) (Box 14)
  - O’Donnell, May O’Donnell Concert Dance Company, 1981, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Oberlin Dance Company/San Francisco, circa 1994, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Olive, Nuria, 1986, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Omolare, Kombo, 1982, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Ontological-Hysteric Theatre, Publicity, 1972-1973, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Paper Bag Players, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Park, Hae Joon, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Park, Ilkyu, 1988, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Park, Rosemary, 1962, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Parker, Carol, 1993, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Parker, Carol, 1993, (35 mm slides) (Box 30)
  - Parker, David (YCC), 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Parker, David (YCC), 1993, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Parrao, Raul, 1992, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Parson, Annie B., 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Parson, Annie-B, 1995, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Parsons Dance Company, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Parsons Dance Company, 1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Parsons Dance Company, 1998, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Patterson, Kraig, 2002, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Patterson, Radonna, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Paxton, Steve, 1994, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Paxton, Steve, 1994, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Pearson, Jerry, 1980, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Pelton, Stephen (YCC), 1994, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Pelton, Steven (YCC), 1994, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Pennison, Marleen, 1985, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Pennsylvania Dance Company, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Pepelyaev, Alexandre (ICCP), 2002, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Perez, Rudy Perez Dance Theater, 1971, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Perez, Rudy, 1972, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Performance Group, undated, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Perm Municipal Theater, 1994, (prints) (Box 14)
  - Perm Municipal Theatre, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Philadanco, 1988, 1999, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Philadanco, 1999, undated, (35 mm slide, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 30)
  - Philadanco, Publicity, undated, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Philadelphia Quartet, undated, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pick Up Performance Company, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 31)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, 1978, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 31)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, 1984-1985, undated, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, 1987, 1990, 1993, (35 mm slides) (Box 31)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, 1994, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, 1997, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, 1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, 1999, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, 2000, (35 mm slides, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, 2002, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, Performance, 1984-1988, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, Performance, 1992-1994, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, Performance, 1995-1997, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, Performance, 1999-2000, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, Performance, 2001-2002, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, Publicity, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, Publicity, 1979, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, Publicity, 2000, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, Publicity, Photographer: Clemens Kalischer, undated, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, Publicity, Photographer: Lois Greenfield, circa 1987, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, Publicity, Photographer: Martha Swope, circa 1984, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, Publicity, Photographer: Michael O’Neill, circa 1988, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, Publicity, undated, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, undated, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 31)
  - Pinska, Klarna, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 31)
  - Pinska, Klarna, 1982, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pinto, Inbal, 1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Pomare, Eleo, 1966, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Porter, Claire, undated, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Posin, Katherine, undated, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Posin, Kathryn Posin Dance Company, 1974, undated, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Preljocaj, Angelin, circa 1995, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Preljocaj, Le Ballet, 1995, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Preljocaj, Le Ballet, 1995, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Price, Sherone, 1997, 2000-2001, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Price, Sherone, 1997-1998, (35 mm slide, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Price, Sherone, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Primus, Pearl, 1943, 1988, 1991, undated, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pucci, Peter Pucci Plus Dancers, 1990, (35 mm slides) (Box 31)
  - Pucci, Peter, 1990, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Pulvermacher, Neta, 1987, (prints) (Box 15)
  - Race, Lisa, 1997, 1999, 2001, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Race, Lisa, 1997, 2002, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Ragen, Ronnie, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 31)
  - Redding-Jones, Renee, 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Redlich, Don, 1955, 1967, undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Redlich, Don Redlich Dance Company, 1974, 1977, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Redlich, Don Redlich Dance Company, 1974, 1977, undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Reinhart, Ariane, 2002, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Reinhart, Ariane, 2002, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Reinhart, Charles, 1961, (35 mm b&w contact sheet) (Box 31)
  - Reinhart, Charles, 1978, 1985-1986, 1998, undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Reinhart, Charles, ADF Tour, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 31)
  - Reinhart, Charles, Headshots, 1982, 1985, 1993, undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Reinhart, Charles, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negatives, 35 mm transparencies) (Box 31)
  - Reinhart, Charles and family, 1976, (35 mm b&w contact sheets, 8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 31)
  - Reinhart, Charles and Laura Dean Company, 1980, (35 mm slides, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Reinhart, Charles and Stephanie, 1993-1994, 1999, undated, (35 mm slide, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Reinhart, Charles and Stephanie, circa 1979, 1984, circa 1993, 1998, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Reinhart, Stephanie, 1985, 1994, 1998, 2001, undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Reinhart, Stephanie, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 31)
  - Reyes, Susan, 1992, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Rhodes, Larry, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 31)
  - Rhodes, Larry, 1981, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Ridiculous Theatrical Company, Publicity, 1974, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Rioult, Pascal Rioult Dance Theatre, 2003, (35 mm color contact sheet) (Box 31)
  - Robinson, Chase, 1962, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Robinson, Cleo Parker, 1990, 1998, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Robinson, Cleo Parker, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 31)
  - Robinson, Cleo Parker Robinson Dance Ensemble, 1990, (35 mm slides) (Box 31)
  - Robinson, Cleo Parker Robinson Dance Ensemble, 1990, 1992, 1994, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Robinson, Cleo Parker Robinson Dance Ensemble, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Robinson, Cleo Parker Robinson Dance Ensemble, 1994, 1995, 1998, undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Robinson, Cleo Parker Robinson Dance Ensemble, 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Robinson, Cleo Parker Robinson Dance Ensemble, 1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Robinson, Cleo Parker Robinson Dance Ensemble, 1998, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Rogers, Helen Priest, 1957, 1961, undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Rogers, Helen Priest, 1964-1965, (35 mm slides, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Romero, Lidia, 1985, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Roosevelt, Jeannette Schlottman, 1961, 1962, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Rosen, Amy Sue (YCC), 1994, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Rosen, Amy Sue, 1990, 1994, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Ross, Bertram and Helen McGenee, 1961, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Roth, Joe, undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Rovira, Maria (ICCP), 1996, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Rovira, Maria, 1997, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Rovira, Maria, 1997, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 31)
  - Rudko, Doris, 1961, undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Rudko, Doris, 1965, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 32)
  - Rudner, Sara, 1969, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Runde, Monica, 1994, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Runde, Monica, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Sadoff, Simon, undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Sailer, Annie Sailer Dance Company, 1988, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Saint Paul Chamber Orchestra, 1974, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Saleem, Kahlid, 2000, (prints) (Box 16)
  - San Martin Ballet, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative, 4 x 5 b&w negative) (Box 32)
  - Sanford, Terry, 1988, 1997, undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Sanford, Terry, 1997, (35 mm slides) (Box 32)
  - Saporta, Compagnie Karine Saporta, 1982-1983, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Satki, Boi, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Scanlon, Jennifer, undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Schmid-Pernette, Compagnie Schmid-Pernette, 1995, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Schmid-Pernette, Compagnie Schmid-Pernette, 1995, 1998, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Schmid-Pernette, Compagnie Schmid-Pernette, 1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Schneider, Maria, circa 1998, (35 mm slide) (Box 32)
  - Schonberg, Bessie, 1937, undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Schonberg, Bessie, 1964, (35 mm slides) (Box 32)
  - School of American Ballet, 1971, 1974, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Schulkind, Marcus, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 32)
  - Schwartz, Ray, 1998, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Scripps, Samuel H., undated, (prints) (Box 16)
  - Self, Jim, 1977, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Sen, Surupa, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Shang, Ruby, 1986, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Shang, Ruby Shang and Company, 1984, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Shankar, Amala, undated, (2 1/4 b&w contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Shankar, Ravi, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Shankar, Uday Shankar India Cultural Center Dance Company, 1984, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Shankar, Uday, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Shankar, Uday Shankar India Culture Centre Dance Company, 1984, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Shankar, Uday Shankar India Culture Centre, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Shapiro, Lynn (YCC), 1994, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Shapiro, Lynn, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Sharma, Bharat, 1984, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Sharma, Sangeesta, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Shawn, Ted, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 32)
  - Shawn, Ted, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Shawn, Ted Shawn Male Dancers, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Shawn, Ted Shawn Male Dancers,undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Shen Wei (ICCP), 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Shen Wei, 1995, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Shen Wei, 2000, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Shen Wei, 2000, (35 mm slides) (Box 32)
  - Shen Wei, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Shen Wei, 2002, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Sherman, Maxine, 1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Shevtzov, Evgeny (ICR), 1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Siegart, Orila, 1994, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Silesian Dance Theater, 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Silesian Dance Theatre, 1993, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Silvers, Sally, 1990, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Silvers, Sally Silvers and Dancers, 1984-1986, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 32)
  - Silvers, Sally Silvers and Dancers, 1988, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Silviera, Domingo, 1985, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Sims, Sandman, 1979, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Sims, Sandman, 1979, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 32)
  - Skaggs, Sarah, 1990, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Skelton, Tom, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Skura, Stephanie, 1984, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Slayton, Jeff, 1986, 1988, 1994, 1996, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Slayton, Jeff, 1994, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Smok, Pavel, 1988, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Soares, Janet, 1965, (2 1/4 b&w contact sheet) (Box 32)
  - Soares, Janet, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Soco, Felipe de, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Sofras, Pam, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 32)
  - Sokolow, Anna, 1975, 1988, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Sokolow, Anna, 1984, (5 x 7 b&w negative) (Box 32)
  - Solomons, Gus Jr., 1982, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Solomons, Gus Jr., 1998, (35 mm slides) (Box 32)
  - Sriman, Sukarji, 1991, 2001, (prints) (Box 17)
  - St. Dennis, Ruth and Ted Shawn, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Starr, Kay, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Stein, Leah, 1988, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Stekelman, Ana Maria, 1998, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Stekelman, Ana Maria, 1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Stewart, Melanie, 1988, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Streb, 1998, (35 mm slide, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Streb, Elizabeth Streb/Ringside, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Streb, Elizabeth Streb/Ringside, circa 1994, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Streb/Ringside, 1998, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Stroman, C. Scoby, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Suando, Endo, circa 1989, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Suando, Endo, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 32)
  - Suber, Bryan, 1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Sungsoo, Ann (YCC), 1993, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Sutki, 1989, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Sutki, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 32)
  - Sutton, James, 1986, 1988, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Suvannanonda, Bancha (ICW), 1993, (35 mm slides) (Box 32)
  - Szony, Francois, circa 1980, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Takei, Kei Takei’s Moving Earth, circa 1983, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Takei, Kei, 1980, (35 mm slides, 8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 32)
  - Takei, Kei, 1984, (4 x 5 b&w negative) (Box 32)
  - Tambutti, Susana, 1990, 1996, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Tambutti, Susan, 1996, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Tamiris, Helen, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 32)
  - Tamiris, Helen, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Tangokinesis, 1998, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Tangokinesis, 1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Tanner, Virginia Tanner's Children's Dance Theatre, 1953, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Tanner, Virginia, undated, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Tarnay, Linda 1988, 1997, 2000, (prints) (Box 17)
  - Tarnay, Linda, 1984, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Tarnay, Linda, 1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 32)
  - Taylor 2, (prints) (Box 18)